欢迎加入OCR小组 qq群906722936 字幕优先发布于群内 字幕广告招租 商业合作Q:1585235535
别这样 卡尔文 放轻松 宝贝
Come on, Calvin, j- just relax, baby.
我怎么放轻松
How can I relax?
我们儿子可能把人女孩肚子搞大了
Our son may have gotten a woman pregnant,
而且他还没结婚
and he's not even married.
我们还怎么直视牧师的双眼
How are we gonna look our pastor in the eye?
我们
We?
你去年复活节就没见过人家了
You haven't looked him in the eye since last Easter.
别 洗手间有人
No! Somebody's using the bathroom.
抱歉 很抱歉
I'm s- - Imsorry. I'm so sorry.
但请你走开
But, please, go away.
所以 有结果了吗
So, do you see anything yet?
还没有
Not yet.
好吧 你要知道
Okay, just so you know,
无论发生了什么 我都会支持你
whatever happens, I will support you
如果我没怀孕 你有什么好支持的
Why would you need to support me if it's negative?
我不知道 姑娘 我也是头一回啊
I don't know, girl. I ain't never done this before!
你有啥好害怕的 肚子里长了小人的
Why are you freaking out? I'm the one
是我又不是你
who might have another human growing inside me.
而且我都定好了今年夏天坎昆度假的行程
And I already prepaid a trip to Cancun this summer.
我有旅游保险不假
I mean, I have travel insurance,
但人家不会理赔无保护性行为的
but I don'tthink it covers unprotected sex!
-好热啊  -对吧
Ooh, is hot? Right? !
这里真的好热
It's hot in herel
我一直以为 自已第一个孩子降生时
I always thought when I had my first kid,
我会有房子 有狗 有老婆
I- I'd have a house, a dog, a wife,
和一支属于我自己的无人赛车队
my own drone racing team.
-验孕棒时间到了  -好吧
Oh, that's the pee stick. Okay.
哦 两条粉红色的线
Oh. Two pink lines.
欢迎来到本社区 欢迎来到这一带
♪'Welcome to the block, welcome to the neighborhood ♪
欢迎跟我们做街坊
♪Welcome to the hood.♪
真不敢相信 我可爱无辜的小宝贝
I can't believe my sweet, little, innocent baby boy
就要当爸爸了
is gonna be a father.
我知道 妈妈 我也不敢相信
I know, Mommy. I can't believe it, either.
我一直以为 就算我哪个孩子
If you had told me one of our sons
要未婚生子
would have had an oops baby,
那也一定是马尔科姆
I would have guessed it'd be Malcolm.
哟哟 行啊 都冲我来吧
Uh, yeah, okay, sure, lash out at me.
这个小流氓又不是我养大的
I didn't raise that little rawdogger.
-你知道吗  -不不不不
You know what? - No, no, no, no.
加尔文 加尔文 加尔文 够了
Calvin, Calvin, Calvin, stop it
你给我闭嘴
You just shut up.
别理他 马蒂
Ignore him, Marty.
妈妈知道 你现在心里
Look, Mommy knows that you're going
一定五味杂陈
through a lot of feelings right now,
但我们时间不多了
but we're running out of time,
我们得把婚礼的日子定一下
so we got to pin down a wedding date.
婚礼
Wedding?
妈 我跟你说了 我们根本没在谈恋爱
Mom, I told you, we're not even in a relationship
这有关系吗
What does that have to do with anything?
妈 你也别太怪他了
Okay, look, go easy on him, Ma.
对到处播种的尼克·坎农来说 今天已经够糟糕了
It's been a rough day for lil' Nick Cannon.
嘿 邻居们
Hey, neighbors.
情况如何
How are we doing?
我们带了香槟和伏特加
We brought champagne and vodka.
一瓶用来庆功 一瓶用来
Depending on whether we're celebrating or,
压惊
uh, freaking out.
准奶奶想开瓶香槟 来吧
Grandma could use some of that bubbly, baby.
谢谢你
Thank you.
妈 你认真的吗
Mom, really?
抱歉 我是太激动了
I'm sorry, I'm just excited
马上要有个小孙女了
that I'm getting a little granddaughter.
你这就知道性别了
You already know the sex?
嗯 还未正式公布
Well, not officially,
但她肯定怀的是女孩
but she's definitely having a girl.
她肚子很高
She's carrying high.
人家根本还没显怀呢
She's not even showing.
那是你看不出来
Not to you.
听着 这都不重要
Look, it doesn't even matter.
“重要的是我要有宝宝了
The important thing is I'm getting a baby.
我要迎来宝宝了
I'm- I'm having a baby.
考特尼怀了我的宝宝
Courtney is having my baby.
你们懂我意思的
You know what I mean!
抱 抱歉 你
I- I'm, I'm sorry, did, uh,
你是说考特尼吗
did you say Courtney?
-是的  -是的
Yeah. - Yeah.
在熔丝盒工作的考特尼
So Courtney, who works at the Fusebox,
是
is the, uh
孩儿她妈么
baby mama?
baby rama?
戴夫可以说“孩儿她妈”么
Can Dave say "baby mama"?
不算种族歧视
It's not racist.
但听着怪怪的
But I don t like it.
是啊 老兄 你为啥要这么问
Yeah, man, why do you ask?
没什么 没什么
No reason. It's nothing.
等等
Hold on.
你这神情和语气
Because the way you're saying it
听起来不像没事的样了
doesn't sound like nothing.
就是吧 以我多年人力资源的经验来看
It's just my HR experience talking.
考特尼理论上是可以起诉熔丝盒的
Theoretjcally, Courtney could sue the Fusebox for everything.
当然 这只是理论上
But that's only in theory and
除非她是那种想要
only if she's the type of person
大捞一笔的人
who wants a ton of money.
谁不是这种人啊 戴夫
Well, that's everybody, Dave.
马蒂 你当时究竟想啥呢
Marty, what were you thinking?
本来就是一夜情 而且发生在
It was a one- time thing and it happened
考特尼进公司之前啊
before Courtney even worked at the Fusebox.
我才不像马尔科姆跟同事乱搞好吗
I'm not like Malcolm, sleeping with my colleagues at work.
什么 行行行
What? l Okay, okay.
瞧 他总是这样
Yeah, see, he always does this.
办了错事就把矛头指向我
Deflects onto me when he screws up.
我们十几岁那次就是 你把妈的车撞坏了
Just like when we were teenagers and you dented Mama's car
竟然先告状 “马尔科姆房里藏了把烟枪“
and screamed, "Uh, Malcolm's got a bong in his room. "
我天呐 那东西真的好呛
My God, the smell from that thing
顺便说下 妈 那烟枪他还放房里呢
By the way, Mama, he's still got that bong in his room.
马尔科姆 我让你把它扔掉的
Malcolm! I told you to get rid of that!
马蒂把女生肚子搞大了 妈妈
Marty got a girl pregnant, Mom!
你最好管好你的嘴
Okay, you better watch your tongue.
戴夫 你都听到了吗
Dave, are you listening to this?
吸毒 车祸 怀孕
Bongs and car wrecks and pregnancies.
我们的格罗弗将来也会这样吗
Is this what we have to look forward to with Grover?
哦天 当然不会
Oh, oh, God, no.
我们父母当得一定比他们强
No, we're gonna do a much better job as parents.
无意冒犯 卡尔文
No offense, Calvin.
不劳远送了
I'll do it.
出去 戴夫
Get out, Dave.
珍玛 我有个好消息
Ooh, Gemma, I have great news.
咱们爱看的剧终于更新了
New episode of our show just dropped.
新一集的《血潮》吗
Ooh, a new Blood Tide?
我最爱谋杀剧了
I love murder.
知道吗我有个理论
You know, I have a theory.
捕虾船上那具尸体 找觉得是唐
The body in the shrimp boat, I think it's Don.
虽然我们只看到了鞋了
You know, we only saw his shoes.
但我们都知道 唐爱穿皮鞋
And we know Don loves leather.
对哦“他还对贝类过敏
Oh, right, and he has a shellfish allergy, too.
我的猜测竟然比想象中还合理
My theory is even smarter than I thought.
我去热袋三明治
I'm gonna go nuke the Hot Pockets.
你把电视设置调好
You get the TV on the right input.
那个我总是弄不好
I can never figure that out.
什么 现在吗
What- what, now?
我现在不能看
I can't watch it now.
但新一集上线都一小时了
But it's already been out for an hour.
我连社媒都不敢上了
I won't be able to go on social media.
珍玛 求你别这么对我
Gemma, don't do this to me.
我得去学校开董事会
I have that board of trustees meeting at school.
切 可不是吗 开会当然更重要了
Oh, of course, yeah, I suppose that's more important.
二位 没被打扰到把
Hey, guys. Am I interrupting anything?
-打扰到了马尔科姆 我们正忙  -很好
Yes, Malcolm, actually, you are. - Well, that's great. I'll only be
我只占用你们一分钟 谢了戴夫
one second. Thank you, Dave.
听着 我只想让你帮忙分析下
Listen, I just needed some clarification
我跟詹妮尔约会的事
on the whole dating Janelle situation.
我知道我们是同事 但詹妮尔并不是
I know that we work together, but it's not like
我的下属 所以我们没问题的
Janelle works for me, so I'm in the clear.
-对吗  -你俩都在南加大工作
Right? - Well, you both work at USC,
所以我说不好
so I don't know.
你们正式公开过关系吗
Have you officially disclosed your relationship?
额 我们有时候会在走廊搂搂抱抱
Uh, I mean, well, we do make out in the hallway sometimes,
所以算是公开过了吧
so I feel like it's kind of out there.
在走廊
In the hallway?
这种事儿要去办公室做呀
You got to move that stuff into your office.
是吧戴夫
Right, Dave?
你可能需要提交一份
You probably just need to file
关系披露表格
some sort of relationship disclosure form.
但这样感觉好正式啊
But that'll make it so formal, man.
我俩目前的关系正正好 好吗
Look, right now it is great, okay?
我早上不给她发短信 没问题
I don't text her in the morning, no problem.
但一旦贴上这个标签 我再不给她发短信
But once I put that label on it and don't text her,
那就有苦头了
then we got beef.
你要是想保住工作
Well, if you want to keep your job,
可能就要把这苦头吞下
you may have to eat the beef.
填份表吧大哥
J- Just sign the form!
-好  -谢谢你 戴夫
Yes. Thank you, Dave.
-好吧  -我和你一起出去
AII right. - I'll walk out with you.
行吧 那就留我
AlI right. DAVE: Great, I'll just
孤单在家 不能看电视
be here alone without the television
也吃不了三明治了
or Hot Pockets.
我看一下前情提总是可以的吧
Guess it won't hurt just to watch the recap.
《血潮》前情提要
NARRATOR: Previously on Blood Tide
根据协定第七节
Pursuant to section seven of the agreement,
协议各方同意对熔丝盒及其法律所有者
"all parties agree to indemnify in perpetuity
和所有合法合作伙伴
"the Fusebox and all legal ownership partners
提供持续的金融保护
"from any legal action resulting
以防止因业务内或外的互动
”from interactions that occurred in or outside
而产生的任何法律后果或责任
the aforementioned business.
看到了吗 多简单
See? Simple.
不不 刚这一堆是什么意思
No! No what does that even mean?
我不知道 马蒂
I don't know, Marty.
我刚告诉我们律师
I just told our lawyers
你跟一个员工搞得很别扭
you got freaky with an employee.
他说得让她签了这个
He said get her to sign that.
谈恋爱从何时起变成了填文书
Since when do relationships come with so much paperwork?
我跟詹妮尔也有一堆表格要填
I got the same thing here with Janelle.
你俩是不知道还有
You two do know there's a thing called
“去酒吧认识女人”这回事吧
"meeting a woman in a bar, "right?
别 别吃那个
Don, don't eat that.
酸橘汁腌鱼里有虾啊
The ceviche has shrimp in it.
你会过敏的
You'll go into anaphylactic sho- -
你的肾上腺素笔被妮可清空了
And Nicole emptied your EpiPen.
爸 你能小点声吗
Dad, can you keep it down?
哦抱歉 伙计 你在做作业吗
Oh, sorry, buddy. You doing your homework?
好的
Sure.
这不是你跟妈一起看的那个剧吗
Isn't this the- the show you watch with Mom?
这个剧啊 额
This show? Uh...
对 但我看的是预告
Yeah, but...this is just a preview.
上面说你看了37分钟
It says you've watched 37 minutes
这个预告片好长的
Well, it's a, it's a long preview.
但你知道吗
But you know what?
这事不必让你妈妈知道
You don't have to tell Mom about this.
说的对
You're right.
我没必要告诉她
I don't have to tell her.
但说谎是不对的
But lying is wrong.
你刚还谎称在做作业啊
You just lied about doing your homework.
一天撒两次谎也太不像话了
Right, and- and two lies would be a lot.
你还想让我去天堂吗 爸
Y- You want me to go to heaven, don't you, Dad?
少废话吧你 你想要什么
Cut the crap, kid. What do you want?
我想把宵禁时间改到晚12点
I want to bump my curfew to midnight.
还想养条宠物蛇
And get a pet snake.
不可能
No way.
那就10点 养只仓鼠
10: 00 and a hamster.
十点半 一只蜥蜴
10: 30 and a lizard.
成交
Deal.
棒球教练来找我练了
The hitting coach is here to hit on me.
不不不
No. No, no, no. Um...
我跟戴夫谈过了 你知道
You know, Iwas talking to Dave, and, uh, you know,
他是人力资源方面的专家 对吧
he knows a whole lot of that, uh, HR stuff, right?
他觉得我们需要
And he was thinking that we need
向大学报告
to register our situation
我们的情况
with the university.
你说的情况是指
And by situation, you mean?
这个 这个情况
This, this thing.
我们 你知道的 在一起了
How- how we are, to you know, uh, together.
-是的  -是的
Yeah. Yeah.
你想说的那个词是“关系”吧
I think the word you're looking for is"relationship. "
我本来想说“暧昧”的
I was gonna go with the word"vibe. "
不过 对
Yeah. But
也可以用“关系”这个词
yeah, Imean, we can go with"relationship, "yeah.
但我不想让你觉得 是我在主导这一切
But- but I don't want you to think I'm trying to push
不是我
that issue, okay? It is not me.
这是上面的意思
This is coming from the top.
-哦 上面  -对的
Oh, "the top"? - Yeah.
哇哦
Wow. Yikes!
我们可不能让上面生气啊
We don't want to mess with the top.
好吧 好吧 听着
Okay, okay, all right, listen.
我只是不想让咱俩丢了工作 就为了这么一段
I'm trying to make sure we don't lose our jobs over this...
你知道的
you know.
-暧昧吗  -是的
This vibe? - Yes.
你懂的
You get it.
等我们签了字再亲
Not till we sign.
万一上面在监视呢
The top could be watching.
你是害怕我起诉你吗
You're worried Im going to sye you?
You're worried I'm going to sue you?
我吗 不 完全不担心
Me? No, no, not at all.
恩 是我爸担心 对
Uh, my dad, quite a bit, yes.
行吧 告诉你爸
Well, you know what, tell your dad
让他放心 我对他
not to worry, Im not after
宝贵的财富没兴趣
his precious money.
谢谢你
Thank you.
谢谢你的理解和配合
Thank you for being so chill about this.
不 该我谢你
Hey, thank you.
真是帮我下定了决心
This really helps me make my decisior
那就好
Oh, good.
请问是啥决心啊
Uh, what decision is that?
这次怀孕打了我一个措手不及
You know, this pregnancy really caught me off guard,
我本来不知该怎么办
and I didn't know what to do.
要不要孩子么
Oh, a- about having the baby?
不不不 我会留下孩子的
Oh, no. No, no, no. I'm having this baby.
只不过我的家人不在身边 我不知
I just didn't know how I was going to raise a baby
该如何把孩子养大
so far from my family.
但现在 看到你和你家人这么不靠谱
But now, seeing how you and your family are tripping,
我觉得我还是回家吧
I realize Im better off going back home.
回卡尔加里吗
To Calgary?
对
Yes.
但那在加拿大
But that's in Canada.
我知道啊
Yeah, I'm aware.
我本来不想回去的
And I had no intention of going back there,
但回到卡尔加里 至少
but in Calgary, me and my baby
我和宝宝会有家人在身边帮衬
will be surrounded by my family, who will be supportive.
不像你家人 把我当成拜金女
Unlike your family, who thinks I'm a gold digger.
不是的
No.
不 我们家也不都这样
No, not- not my whole family.
只有我爸 还有我邻居戴夫
Just my dad. A- And my neighbor Dave.
天啊 一想到今晚新剧集的走向
Ooh! I'm so nervous about what's gonna happen
我精神都紧张
on tonight's new episode.
真不知道你怎么能吃得下
I don't know how you can eat.
我午餐没怎么吃 珍玛
Well, I had a light lunch, Gemma.
肚子饿是完全正常的
My being hungry is perfectly normal.
-好的 开始吧  -好 开始了
Okay, start it. Start it. Okay, here we go.
啊 你觉得接下来会怎样
Ugh! What do you think's gonna happen?
嗯 这
Well, it's
这很难说 真的
it's hard to say, really.
天啊 好烫
Oh, my God, that's hot.
好烫
Hot
三明治好烫啊
The Hot Pocket's hot.
小声点 我都听不见船长在说什么了
I can't hear what the fishing boat captain is saying.
不重要
It's not important.
你怎么知道不重要
How do you know?
呃 我我 我不知道
Uh, II don't- - I don't. I don't know.
我怎么会知道 我对这一集一无所知
How- how would I? I don't know anything about this episode. Oh.
也许很重要呢
You know, maybe it was important.
-你想倒回去吗 那我倒回去  -闭嘴 你还在讲话
Do you want to go back? - I should go back. - No, y- you're still talking,
现在只能倒回去了
so now we have to go back.
我要坦白一件事
I have something to confess.
一件可怕的事
Something horrible.
怎么了
What?
哦天
Oh, man.
接下来要惨了
This is gonna be rough.
这样吧 让我先接个电话
You know what? Let me get that first.
干嘛 不用接 写着“疑似骚扰电话”
Wha- uh, you better not. It says"spam likely. "
又没写“绝对是骚扰电话”
Well, it doesn't say"spam definitely, "
-让我按一下吧  -不行 戴夫
so let me just answer it. - No, Dave- -
说啊 你到底做了什么 你做了什么
Spit it out, What did you do? What did you do?
我昨晚已经看过这集了 没等你
I watched the episode last night, without you.
这是我们共同的剧 我辜负了你的信任
This was our show, and I violated your trust.
没关系
It's okay.
不 有关系
No, it's not.
我真该死
I deserve to be dead.
跟唐一个下场
Just like Don.
剧透了
Spoilers!
抱歉
I'm sorry.
天啊 真抱歉 我真可恨
God, I'm sorry. God, I'm a monster.
比清空了肾上腺素笔的妮可还可恨
Just like Nicole who emptied the EpiPen.
戴夫
Davel
我配不上你 天 我恨自己这么软弱
I don't deserve you. God, I hate that I'm so weak.
戴夫 别说了
Dave, stop.
说实话 我其实松了一口气
To be honest, I'm a little relieved.
有件事 我一直在找合适的时机
I've been trying to find the right time
告诉你
to tell you this.
最近几个月 你一直在提议
You know how, for months now, you've been saying
一起看电影《芭比》
we should finally watch the Barbie movie,
我的回答总是 今晚不行
and I kept saying, "Not tonight"?
这是因为
That's because.
我没等你 已经先看了
...I saw the movie without you.
你什么
You what?
我跟蒂娜翘班去看了日场
Tina and I snuck off to a matinee.
我很抱歉
I'm- I'm sorry.
你抱歉有什么用 珍玛
Sorry's not gonna cut it, Gemma!
你知道我有多想看《芭比》
You know how badly I wanted to see the Barbie movie.
我博客上的粉丝都在等着
AlI of my blog followers have been waiting
听我的热评
to hear my hot take.
不知道能不能安慰到你
I- If it makes you feel any better,
反正你看了也不会喜欢
you wouldn't have liked it anyway.
-不会吗 烂片吗  -切 你会爱死的
No? It was not good? - No, you would have loved it.
-拍的特别好  -我就知道我会喜欢
- It was so good. - I- I know I would have loved it!
大家都这么说的
That's what everybody says.
好吧
Well.
考特尼把协议签了
Courtney signed the agreement.
你开心了吧
I hope you're happy.
太好了 确实开心
Well, all right, I am happy.
爸 她没打算起诉我们的 但她很伤心
Dad, she wasn't gonna sue us, but she was upset
因为我们把她当成了拜金女
that we thought she was a gold digger.
我才没那么叫她
I never would have called her that.
我没那么粗鲁
I'm not rude.
我只是以为她看上了我的钞票
I just thought she was somebody trying to stick me for my paper.
你的钞票安全了 爸
Well, your paper's safe now, Dad,
因为考特尼要搬回加拿大了
because Courtney's moving back to Canada.
什么 等等 什么
What- what? Wait, what?
她要把我宝宝带去加拿大
She's taking my baby to Canada?
不行不行 太远了
No, no, no that- that's too far.
那里那么冷 白人那么多
That's- that's too cold. That's too white.
宝贝 加拿大也有黑人的
Look, baby, there- there are Black people in Canada.
说两个出来
Name two.
德雷克
Drake,
还有 额 考特尼的妈妈
and, uh, Courtney's mom.
你这下开心了吧 卡尔文
I hope you're happy, Calvin.
-可不是吗  -我没有
He is. N- No, I am not.
宝贝 我们可以
Baby, we can
听着
Look,
我跟考特尼还没商量好
Courtney and I hadn't figured out
如何一起抚养这个孩子
how we were gonna raise this baby together.
我只知道 我想要他俩成为我生活的一部分
AlI I knew is I wanted them to be a part of my life.
我现在既失去了孩子 又失去了朋友
Now I'm losing my friend and my baby.
该死
Damn.
这次我真的搞砸了
I really blew it this time, huh?
没错
Yes, you did.
你要不给我解决好
And if you don't fix it,
就去准备护照和厚外套吧 爷爷
you better get your passport and your puffy coat, Grandpa,
因为我们要搬去加拿大
'cause we're moving to Canada.
96号
Number 96.
到我了
: Oh! That's me.
本文件要求双方签署人都在场
This requires both signatories to be present.
问题就在这
Well, you see, uh, that's the thing.
另一个签署人 她 她还没来
The other signatory, she's, uh, she's not here yet.
97号
Number 97.
等等 哥们儿
Whoa, wait a minute, man.
别别 你先请坐
Hey Whoa, no, no, sit down.
坐 坐下
Sit- sit down.
听着 她马上就到了 好吗
Look, man, she should be here any second, okay?
她八点半有场网球比赛
She had a tennis match at, uh, a- at 8: 30,
也许 也许她打成了平局
and, uh, maybe, maybe she got caught
双方展开了拉锯 耽误了时间
in one of those long deuce situations.
这是有可能的 可以拉锯很久
That can happen. It can go long.
或者
Or, uh
也许她不会来了
...maybe she's not gonna show.
该死 你说她是不是听了太多感情谈话
h, damn, do you think maybe she got cold feet
临阵退缩了
from all the relationship talk?
你在另一个签署人面前也这么粘人吗
Are you this needy with the other signatory?
马尔科姆
Malcolm.
嘿 你来了
Hey. You came.
看 她来了
You see? That's her.
抱歉我迟到了
Sorry I'm late.
我扣球时扭伤了脚踝
I sprained my ankle going for a drop shot.
照顾好她
Take good care of her.
我会的
I will.
谢谢你 先生
Thank you, sir.
你
Do you,
马尔科姆·巴特勒
Malcolm Butler,
你愿意承认所写陈述真实有效吗
attest that the statements written here are true?
我愿意
I do.
詹妮尔·芬奇
And do you, Janelle Finch,
你愿意承认所写陈述真实有效吗
attest that the statements written here are true?
我愿意
I do.
你们的关系披露声明正式通过
Your relationship disclosure is approved.
97号
Number 97.
好的 宝贝
Okay, baby.
你确定不需要我帮忙吗
Now, you sure you don't need my help?
不用 祸是我闯的 也得我来弥补
Yes Look, I caused all this. I need to fix it.
好吧 要是失败了 就给我发个信号
Okay, well, if it's not working, just give me the signal
我会流着泪走进来
and I'll come in with the tears.
我哭成这个熊样 没人会说不的
You know robody can resist my ugly cry.
好了 哦 好的 好的
Oh, okay, ooh, ooh, all right.
好的 好了 好吧
Okay, all right, all right, okay.
希望不需要你放大招
Let's hope it doesn't come to that.
好的 去吧
Okay, come on.
嘿 考特尼
Hey, Courtney?
别担心 我正要走正在收拾东西呢
Don't worry, I'm out of here. I'm just packing up my things.
你拿了不少笔啊
Oh, well, you're taking quite a few pens.
带走吧 把笔带走
Keep the pens. Keep the pens.
听着
Listen, uh,
我能跟你谈谈吗
c- can I talk to you for a second?
还有什么文件需要我签吗
Ah, are those some more papers that you want me to sign?
不 这些是你已经签过的文件
Uh, no. These are the ones you already signed.
嗯
And, um
你千什么
What are you doing?
听着 考特尼 我一时糊涂
Look, Courtney, I was an idiot.
只顾着考虑
I just was thinking about
可能失去这一切 全然忘记
losing all of this, and I forgot about
真正重要的是什么
what was really important.
是什么呢
What's that?
家人
Family.
我的家人 而且我们还壮大了
My family. And it's growing now.
包括你的孩子
I mean, it includes your baby.
说出来有些奇怪 也包括你
And in a weird way, you.
他是想说 我们爱你
He's trying to say, "We Iove you, "
说下去 宝贝 你能行
Oh, go ahead, baby. You got it, you got it,
所以
So...
我真心希望你能改变主意 留下来
I really, really hope you change your mind and stay.
我知道 这也是马蒂的希望
I know Marty does, too.
我保证你不会后悔的
I promise you, y- you won't be sorry.
好吧 我承认 我其实不想回去
Well, I admit, I didn't really want to go back.
那就不要回去 不要回去
Don't go back. Don't go back.
在这里生孩子 瞧 我们有零食
Stay here and have the baby. Look, we got snacks.
有零食 就在这
We got snacks, right here.
等等 你们公司的产假政策是什么
Wait, w- what's your company's maternity leave policy?
-哦 通常来讲  -你说了算
Oh, well, usually...Whatever you want.
对吧 卡尔文
Right, Calvin?
是的 对 没问题 肯定的
Yeah. Yeah, right. Uh cool, yeah. For sure.
-对  -嗯
Yep, yep. Mm- hmm.
一言为定
You got a deal.
-谢天谢地  -好吧 好的 非常好
Oh, thank God. - AlI right. AlI right, very good.
但你得给我签个文件
But I'm- a need that in writing.
挺幽默
Nice one.
呼应 你懂吧
The comeback, you know,
-因为我让她签了文件  -她没笑 卡尔文
because I did the contract...She's not laughing, Calvin.
好吧 我去
Well, damn.
爸 你干什么
Dad, what are you doing, man?
你造成的伤害还不够吗
Haven't you caused enough damage?
没有 马蒂
No, no, Marty.
听着 我道过歉了 她会留下的
Uh, look, I apologized, and she's staying.
是吗
You are?
是的
Yeah.
谁会对10个月的产假说不呢
It's pretty hard to pass up a ten- month maternity leave.
啊 休一年也行
Ah. Take a year.
我的孙子保住了
I got my grandbaby.
: I got my grandbaby
这个发带我非带不可吗
Do I have to wear this headband?
多有意思啊 宝贝
It's fun, baby.
这就是看《芭比》的乐趣啊
It's part of the whole Barbie thing.
可我觉得戴这个好蠢
I just feel like I look stupid.
速食三明治登场
Hot Pocket up.
不了 谢谢 真不用
No, okay, I'm good.
嗨 大卫
Hey, Dave.
哦 你看起来棒极了
Oh, you look great.
你们敢相信 这些东西都是我的吗
Could you guys believe that I already owned all this stuff?
相信
BOTH: Yeah, we can.
手别乱摸 蒂娜
Watch your fingers, Tina.
又不是在咱自己家
We're not at our house.
你说什么呢 卡尔文
What are you talking about, Calvin?
倒不是说我丢了蜥蜴哈
I'm not saying that I lost my lizard,
但你们谁见过一只蜥蜴吗
but have any of you seen a lizard?